Vikentor Pierre

Florida, Orlando (561) 318-9898

Portfolio: www.modevtech.com Email:vikentorpierre@gmail.com

ABOUT

Experienced full-stack web-developer and wordpress developer of 4+ yrs. Am knowledgeable in creating rich modern UI/UX design, debugging, and deploying backend Api solutions. Able to work independently, as well as in a team. For my full portfolio visit www.modevtech.com

EXPERIENCE

Derive System, Orlando -- Product QA/QC

10/ 2018 - PRESENT

An automobile software company that sells car tuners. My job consists of repairing tuners and using SuiteScript(a subset of JavaScript)to collect repair data to present to the CEO.

Vespo, Orlando -- lead Web/los developer

10/ 2018 - 07/2019

Vespo is a small startup form amongst friends including me. I was the lead developer on both the main web application and mobile ios app. I created the backend with node.js, express.js and mongodb. The front-end stack was React.js, Redux, and material.ui. It's a full stack application that use RESTFull api to connect the front and back together.

Mosdevv, Orlando lead Web/los developer

10/ 2015 - PRESENT

Mosdevv is a web/app business I have with my friend. We make websites and apps for clients. Our main front-end stack: Wordpress, React.js, Vue.js, a little bit of Angular, plain HTML5/CSS3 Material.ui, bootstrap, ¡Query. Back-end stack: node.js, express.js, mongodb, postgrest, RESTFull Api. jwt, OAuth.

EDUCATION

Palm Beach State College, (PBSC)

AA Computer Science(CS)

University of Central Florida(UCF)

Currently, On my last two semesters.

SKILLS

Languages

- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Python
- IOS/Swift
- AJAX
- jQuery
- Git
- PHP

Framework

- React.is
- Vue.js
- Wordpress
- Material.ui
- Bootstrap
- Django

More

- Express.js
- API/Rest
- MongoDB
- Deploy
- UI/UX
- SEO
- Agile
- Integratio n Testing

- Node.js
- Postgres
- Hosting
- Figma
- Scripting
- GitHub
- Unit
 - Testing
- Google adwords

INTERESTS

- Data science
- Learning French/Spanish
- Al/ Machine learning
- Decentralize application
- Marketing google and facebook

To obtain my BS In Computer Science(CS)	
•	